the world of direct ticket issuing and
processing was shaken to its Core last
week when Ticket Master the most that's
I'm going to say for now Ticket
Master the most popular ticket seller in
the World Behind Brian ceter sts.com I'm
sure you're all familiar uh they're in
the midst of a class action lawsuit
courts ruled that Ticket Master had to
pay back consumers millions and millions
of dollars in service charges
rather than provide cash refunds though
Ticket Masters offering vouchers and
discount codes that can only be used for
quote eligible events which is Ticket
Master code for citt
events uh here's what Twitter user at
Crypt Tera had to say about it really
excited to use these Free Ticket Master
vouchers to see Keith Urban 17
times could be worse imagine opening
your free vouchers to haven't seen
something like walking on the solay the
Smashmouth cir to solay show
might as well be walking on so
circus all right comedians as a Ticket
Master user please open your tab and
find out what ticket voucher they gave
you Dave Hill two tickets to see
Nickelback also you are in
Nickelback oh wow yeah my voucher puts
me in
Nickelback Mary Holland Mary Holland um
I got front row seats and backstage
passes to third eye blind and I'm not
allowed to say
no thank
you Joe Ran's
next uh oh nice front row seats to Billy
Joel's semiannual prostate
exam up
front I'm going to have to get a big
shot dude yes I would
actually I would actually like to that I
mean I don't know what when when he gets
a prostate exam it's called The
Stranger get it get it one two three 4
[Laughter]
pressure JFK blown away I got a
colost